Mitchell Clement Curriculum Vitae_2020

Personal Info

2A Fairfield Road, Hamilton, New Zealand 027 817 2280 mitchellamitchellclement.com mitchellclement.com 29/05/1999



About

My name is Mitchell Clement and I am currently studying in my final year of Graphic Design at Whitecliffe. Originally from Hamilton I have lived in Auckland for 3 Years. I have strong interpersonal skills proven through my work as a Sales Consultant for Noel Leeming and other brands at showground events. I hold myself to a high standard and would consider myself diligent and hard working. Outside of Graphic Design, I have interests in Photography and Film.

Education

Whitecliffe College of Fine Arts

2018-2020

Bachelor of Fine Art majoring in Graphic Design.

Hamilton Boys High School

2013-2017

NCEA Level 3 - Excellence

NCEA Level 3 - Photography Scholarship

Subjects: Film and Television

Photography Design Architecture English

Awards

- NZ Best Design Awards, Gold, The Perry Line 2020
- AGDA 2020 x3 Merit Awards
- NCEA Level 3 National Photography Schollarship
- NCEA Level 3 Endorsed with Excellence
- Top in Level 3 Photography, & Film and Television
- Photolife Photographers award (2016)

Work History

Noel Leeming

Dec 2015-Present

Te Rapa, Hamilton Branch Auckland Events/ Stores

Role: Sales Consultant

Visual Merchandiser/Regional Store Design

Domino's Pizza 2010-2013

Rototuna, Hamilton Branch

Skills (/5)

Adobe Suite

Photoshop *****
Premiere Pro ****
InDesign *****
Illustrator *****
Bridge ****
Lightroom *

Web Coding ***
Mac OSX *****
Microsoft Office ****

References

Patrick Lenihan, Store Manager Noel Leeming Te Rapa patrick.lenihanānlg.co.nz 027 270 4864 Jonty Valentine,
Former HOD
Whitecliffe - Graphic Design
jontymindex.org.nz